<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Job Search on BabanovBlog</title><link>https://aidarbabanov.github.io/categories/job-search/</link><description>Recent content in Job Search on BabanovBlog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:09:51 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aidarbabanov.github.io/categories/job-search/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Restart</title><link>https://aidarbabanov.github.io/posts/restart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:09:51 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aidarbabanov.github.io/posts/restart/</guid><description>As it often happens, I started actively, but at some point I just abandoned it. I don&amp;rsquo;t even want to comment on the situation, it is so common. It&amp;rsquo;s like I&amp;rsquo;m preparing for an exam. The best motivator is of course the deadline. But there are no deadlines in job seeking. So let&amp;rsquo;s get back to basics. The main thing is to like and not to strain. And the preparation itself began to strain.</description></item><item><title>Helpful Resources Related to MAANG Job Search</title><link>https://aidarbabanov.github.io/posts/helpful-resources/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 16:58:59 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aidarbabanov.github.io/posts/helpful-resources/</guid><description>General information Good guide from Adilet Zhaksylyk: https://interviews.school/ Russian post about preparation: https://habr.com/ru/post/499394/</description></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>https://aidarbabanov.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:40:45 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aidarbabanov.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>What and why? Probably every developer sooner or later decides that he is ready to move forward and try his luck in working for a top company. These companies are called FAANG (Facebook, Amazon, Apple, Netflix and Google). More recently, one company has changed its name. Facebook was renamed Meta. So, technically, the acronym can be changed to MAANG.
I will not write tutorials on how to get into the top company, since there is a lot of such information on the Internet and it will be pointless to create a duplicate of such content.</description></item></channel></rss>